{
    "cards": [
        {
            "back": "1",
            "front": "1*1",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "2",
            "front": "1*2",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "3",
            "front": "1*3",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "4",
            "front": "1*4",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "5",
            "front": "1*5",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "6",
            "front": "1*6",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "7",
            "front": "1*7",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "8",
            "front": "1*8",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "9",
            "front": "1*9",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "10",
            "front": "1*10",
            "points": 1
        },
        {
            "back": "b",
            "front": "What is after a?",
            "points": 2
        }
    ],
    "name": "Default Deck"
}